<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Napkins on Chris Kerwell Gresla</title>
    <link>https://ckgresla.github.io/napkins/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Napkins on Chris Kerwell Gresla</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ckgresla.github.io/napkins/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>An Evolution of Office Attire</title>
      <link>https://ckgresla.github.io/napkins/officeattireevolution/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ckgresla.github.io/napkins/officeattireevolution/</guid>
      <description>​
A case for why you should wear a turtleneck, or at least consciously decide on how you wish to present yourself.
In Summary;
An Integration of Form and Function Casual Elegance The Notion of a Uniform It&amp;rsquo;s Showtime Aesthetics are kind of important, the way your experience in life is embodied is dictated by the ways in which yo
​
Images This is what a turtleneck looks like Gydw1n</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Autoencoders are Thought Translation Machines</title>
      <link>https://ckgresla.github.io/napkins/autoencodersthink/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ckgresla.github.io/napkins/autoencodersthink/</guid>
      <description>​
Learning is about running through data and developing a compressed representation of what you have seen in order to transform experience into knowledge that is useful in the future. If we attempt to learn things that are mundanely literal it kinda ends up being not fun — but having fun whilst learning might be the thing you exactly want to do. (see articles 1 &amp;amp; 2)
The Godfather of Artificial Intelligence, Geoffrey Hinton is infamous for his colorful intuitions that describe phenomena in ways that just freaking click.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is a Napkin?</title>
      <link>https://ckgresla.github.io/napkins/examples/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ckgresla.github.io/napkins/examples/</guid>
      <description>Akin to the &amp;ldquo;Ponderings&amp;rdquo; page, this collection of &amp;ldquo;Napkins&amp;rdquo; is a collection of ideas that I felt were better expressed in a series of paragraphs as opposed to a question.
Some of the world&amp;rsquo;s best ideas were incarnated on a napkin, these might be a few of mine.
​
The rest of this page will be a collection of examples for different features supported in the variant of markdown powering this website &amp;ndash; pretty stuff.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
